この仮定から　紡がれる正解が まだ　出ていない そんな予感 その答えの意外さが 最悪の場合
In the Dentora region of the Republic of Padokea, is a 3,722 meter-high dormant volcano
surrounded by forest, Kukuroo Mountain.
俺達の計画を 全て狂わせそうな… 時間だ。 突入１分前　集まってくれ。
The home of the famous Zoldyck
family of assassins is here.
くそ！　時間がない
Visitors come, every day,
hoping for a glimpse of the mansion that no one has ever seen before.
モラウのげきの　およそ２分前
Hey, I'm back!
東ゴルトー共和国の
He works with me here. Good evening.
はるか上空を飛ぶ怪鳥から ２人の男が飛び降りた
If you managed to win over Zebro,
you must be special.
最初に気付いたのは　ピトー
But I'm not leaving. Not until I see Killua!
上空を見上げた理由を 突き詰めるならば 「何となく」という他ない
When Killua was in trouble,
I wasn't there for him.
しかし　それは数秒後 確信に変わる 敵！
If I had been there, I could have stopped Killua!
しかし　この時 賊は　まだ　はるか上空 ピトーの並外れた感覚器官の どれを持ってしても
Killua is my close friend!
到達は不可能な位置にいた
We understand.
臨戦態勢に入ったピトーが 確信した根拠は
Then why not do some training here? Training? Hey, Zebro...
野生の本能によるものと 言わざるを得ない
Listen to me, Gon-kun. You three are allowed to work together
護衛軍２匹が ここで　ほぼ同時に
Then I'll need you to put these on.
龍！
Please wear it at all times,
except while you sleep.
突入１０秒前。 ９。
Please have some tea.
８。
What the...?
７。
The cups weigh twenty kilograms.
モラウのカウントダウンとともに ゴンの瞳が深く暗く
This teapot weighs forty kilograms. All furniture and utensils in this house
そして 静かに冷たく沈んで行くのを
weigh over twenty kilograms apiece.
横のキルアだけが気付いていた
I see... So this will serve as training. It's useless.
６。
They'll give up in two or three days.
５。
Seaquant, I believe that
your shift has already started. Oh, that's right...
４。
Sorry about that. He isn't a bad person.
３。
Through the door over there.
２。
I'm guessing that
この時 ピトーは「円」を解いた
Yes, it weighs five hundred kilograms. Five hundred?
完全な臨戦態勢に入るために
What?! Get out!
だが… あっ。
I can't hold it in!
「ドラゴンダイヴ」。
Kalluto-chan, open the door.
臨戦態勢によって 「円」を解いたことが裏目に出る
Kil, have you learned your lesson yet?
奴らは!?
It's no use, Mama. He isn't even the least bit sorry.
王への脅威を目の前にし
Milluki! Shut your mouth!
極限まで研ぎ澄まされた ピトーの六感は 容易に自身を 侵入者の元に運んだ
Kil, stop being so stubborn
and say that you're sorry.
降り注ぐ無数の龍よりも
Oh, right. That friend of yours... Gon, was it?
危険なのは あの人間
He'd be better off just leaving, but it sounds like he wants
to try the Testing Gate.
それは　ピトーが全力で戦う時に 発現させる念能力
Listen to me, Kil... You didn't even tell me?!
能力発動から攻撃まで 要する時間は　０．１秒を切る
Don't yell at Mama! I told you to shut your mouth! I didn't think I needed to tell you, Kil...
ホッホッ。 しかし　ピトーは　そのはざま
Since it's impossible for him
to open the front gate.
確かに　聞いた
He'll do it. What?
受け攻め いくつか予想しとったが…。
Gon will open it. Oh, that's nice.
そりゃ悪手だろ　アリんこ。
But he'll still never make it here... Gon will...
死ぬって瞬間に 時間が超スローになって
Wait, Gon!
自分の人生を 振り返る感覚あるじゃろ？
You just watch. Huh? Why?
あれに近い。
You need to let your arm heal first.
むしろ　それより 信ぴょう性は測りやすいぞ。
As long as Kurapika and I can open it,
it doesn't matter.
何しろ　自分じゃなく
Let us handle this!
相手が　その時　思っていたことを 聞き取るんじゃからのう。
Okay. Let's do this, Kurapika! Yeah!
本人の他は　絶対に知り得ぬ情報を 聞くこともあるわけじゃ。 互いが証人よ。
It's impossible...
ある武道では 「心滴拳聴」と呼ばれる現象よ。
No use... It won't budge an inch.
まことの強者同士が ぶつかり合う瞬間には
Damn! But we just started our training.
よくある時間感覚の矛盾じゃ。
If we work hard enough, we can do it! I wish I could share your optimism.
強さの秘密じゃったな。
This will never work.
あとは　そうさな。
You kids need to wake up.
戦闘のほうでいえば 「百式観音」。
In that case, you should quit watching us
and do your job!
これが最も厄介じゃろ。
Gon is one of us.
ネテロの一連の動作は
Okay, let's give it another shot! Yeah!
ピトーは感じたが…
Man, you can't just mindlessly push.
ピトーの念能力の発動から 攻撃までの刹那に
Match your timing.
全てがなされたことに 疑いの余地はなく…
You have to push both doors,
with all your strength, simultaneously. Or the gate won't ever open.
それは　ピトーが己の体感時間を 限りなく圧縮し
Match our timing...
自らの時を止めるに 等しい状態に置くことでしか
And push both doors with all our
strength simultaneously...
ネテロの動きを目で捉えることが できなかったことに起因する
Okay! One! Two! Three!
不可避の速攻である！
It moved.
ネテロ　４６歳
What? The Testing Gate?
己の肉体と武術に限界を感じ
And? Oh, well...
悩みに悩み抜いた結果
I just wanted to let you know.
彼が　たどり着いた先は…
Very well.
感謝であった
He's always so cold.
一日　１万回 感謝の正拳突き！
Damn it...
気を整え　拝み…
It won't move any farther. One last spurt, Leorio...
祈り　構えて…
Got it!
突く！
Gon... Why are you using your left arm?
一連の動作を１回こなすのに 当初は５６秒
Anyway, we have to push together, right? Right, let's push! Here we go!
１万回を突き終えるまでに
Two! Three!
２年が過ぎた頃
That made it painfully clear
異変に気付く
that I wasn't on their level.
ハァ…　ハァ…　ハァ…。
So you decided to work here.
１万回　突き終えても 日が暮れていない
Sorry... But the masters and servants
are all monsters.
齢５０歳を超えて 完全に羽化する
The Testing Gate opened? Yes, ma'am.
感謝の正拳突き　１万回
This is a critical time for Killua. We cannot allow anyone near him!
１時間を切る！
Especially not those unnecessary friends...
んっ？ おぉ!?
If you take one step beyond this line, I'll remove you by force.
気のせいだよな 一瞬…　消えて
Gon! Damn it! Leorio! Kurapika!
音が後から…
Don't interfere. Let me handle this.
館長？
Ow...
か… 観音様が…。
We don't intend to fight you. We just want to see Killua.
さて…。
It doesn't matter what your motives are. I'm simply following my orders.
いいよ　飯　おごってくれたらな。
You can try all you want.
今から６０年以上 昔のことである
I'll never let you pass.
治療意外には 全く使い道のない能力である 「ドクターブライス」は 発現させた場所から
Stop it.
移動ができず
Stay away!
行動半径が ２０ｍほどに限られる
Cut it out!
ににに…。
Don't you realize how futile this is?! Why don't you stop him?
にににに…！
Aren't you his friends?
ピトー離脱の窮地を救った
What's the problem?
止まった…
I'm just here to see my friend.
早く！
Why do I have to do this?!
そこで彼らが目にしたのは 計画時には　誰しもが そこに居るとは 考えもしなかった ユピーの姿だった
But now, they face their
greatest obstacle yet. A sad message from Killua, saying that he can't see them.